Guide to the Media Services Audio and Video Recordings, 1963 - ongoing UA.10.03.0003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA2011-0007, 4
  - Divinity School Duke Chapel to Goodson Chapel Dedication, switched show, 2005 October 11 (3 tapes); DVCAM (Box 19, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0048)
  - Divinity School Duke Chapel to Goodson Chapel Dedication, walk from one to the other outside, 2005 October 11; betacam (Box 19, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0106)
  - Divinity School Duke Chapel to Goodson Chapel Dedication, walk from one to the other outside, 2005 October 11; DVCAM (Box 19, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0058)
  - Divinity School Duke Chapel to Goodson Chapel Dedication, walk from one to the other outside, 2005 October 11; DVCAM (Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0095)
  - Duke Children's Classic, Page Auditorium, edited show, 2000 May 19; DVCAM (Box 19, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0043)
  - DUMC 75th Special Nasher Dinner, 2006 September 25; DVCAM (Box 19, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0051)
  - DUMC 75th Special Nasher Dinner, B-roll, 2006 September 25; mini-dv (Box 19, Video-cassette UA10030003-MiniDV-0005)
  - Founder's Day, 2009 October 1; DVCAM (Box 19, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0056)
  - Kristina Johnson, Dean - Pratt School of Engineering, Interview, B-roll, 2003 June 16; DVCAM (Box 19, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0044)
  - President Richard Brodhead, Conversation with Gross Scholarship Recipients, 2006 November 16; betacam (Box 19, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0107)
  - President Richard Brodhead, Conversation with Gross Scholarship Recipients, 2006 November 16; betacam (Box 19, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0108)
  - Provost Peter Lange, Remarks on Kristina Johnson, 2003 June 17; DVCAM (Box 19, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0045)
  - Soledad O'Brien, 2009 January 22; DVCAM (Box 19, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0054)
  - York to Goodson Closing Convocation, 2005 April 20; mini-dv (Box 19, Video-cassette UA10030003-MiniDV-0004)
  - York to Goodson Closing Convocation, Mike's camera, 2005 April 20; DVCAM (Box 19, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0047)
  - York to Goodson Closing Convocation, Tom's camera, 2005 April 20; DVCAM (Box 19, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0046)
- Accession UA2014-0018, 5
  - Admissions Video - Duke Divinity School, circa 1993-1997; betacam-sp (Box 20, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0114)
  - Building Community: Conversations on Race with Robert Reich, 1997 November 17; betacam-sp (Box 21, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0132)
  - Campaign For Duke Package, 1998 October 2; betacam-sp (Box 20, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0116)
  - Celebrating The Past, Charting The Future, 2013 January 26; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0093)
  - College Is Possible, 1999 October 30; betacam-sp (Box 20, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0117)
  - College Is Possible, 1999 October 30; betacam-sp (Box 20, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0118)
  - Did 9/11 Change Anything? Everything?, 2011 September 11; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0085)
  - Duke Alumni Assocation - Duke B-ball Forum, 2011 April 8; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0081)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, 2003 May 10; betacam-sp (Box 22, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0008)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, 1993 May 14; 3/4-inch (Box 20, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0061)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, 1993 May 14; 3/4-inch (Box 20, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0062)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, 1991 May 10; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0054)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #1, 2005 May 13; betacam-sp (Box 22, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0012)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #1, 1999 May 14; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0048)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 2004 May 8; betacam-sp (Box 22, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0010)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 2005 May 14; betacam-sp (Box 22, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0013)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 2001 May 12; DVCAM (Box 22, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0015)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 2002 May 11; DVCAM (Box 22, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0018)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 2004 May 8; DVCAM (Box 22, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0022)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 2004 May 8; DVCAM (Box 22, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0023)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 2005 May 14; DVCAM (Box 22, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0027)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 2007 May 12; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0064)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 2008 May 10; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0065)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 2009 May 9; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0069)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 2010 May 15; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0073)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 2011 May 14; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0082)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 2012 May 12; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0090)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 1997 May 17; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0046)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 1998 May 16; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0047)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 1999 May 15; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0049)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #2, 2000 May 13; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0051)
  - Duke Baccalaureate Service, #3, 2006 May 13; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0060)
  - Duke Chapel - Palm/Passion Sunday Service, 2003 April 3; DVCAM (Box 22, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0020)
  - Duke Commencement, 1999 May; betacam-sp (Box 22, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0006)
  - Duke Commencement, 2000 May 14; betacam-sp (Box 22, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0007)
  - Duke Commencement, 2006 May 14; betacam-sp (Box 22, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0014)
  - Duke Commencement, 1993 May 16; betacam-sp (Box 20, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0113)
  - Duke Commencement, 1990 May 13; betacam-sp (Box 20, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0120)
  - Duke Commencement, 1993 May 16; betacam-sp (Box 21, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0122)
  - Duke Commencement, 1994 May 8; betacam-sp (Box 21, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0123)
  - Duke Commencement, 1994 May 8; betacam-sp (Box 21, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0124)
  - Duke Commencement, 1995 May 14; betacam-sp (Box 21, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0125)
  - Duke Commencement, 1995 May 14; betacam-sp (Box 21, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0126)
  - Duke Commencement, 1996 May; betacam-sp (Box 21, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0127)
  - Duke Commencement, 1997 May 18; betacam-sp (Box 21, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0130)
  - Duke Commencement, 1997 May 18; betacam-sp (Box 21, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0131)
  - Duke Commencement, 1998 May; betacam-sp (Box 21, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0133)
  - Duke Commencement, 2001 November 4; DVCAM (Box 22, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0016)
  - Duke Commencement, 2002 May 12; DVCAM (Box 22, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0019)
  - Duke Commencement, 2003 May 11; DVCAM (Box 22, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0021)
  - Duke Commencement, 2004 May 9; DVCAM (Box 22, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0024)
  - Duke Commencement, 2005 May 15; DVCAM (Box 22, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0028)
  - Duke Commencement, 2006 May 14; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0061)
  - Duke Commencement, 2006 May 14; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0062)
  - Duke Commencement, 2008 May 11; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0067)
  - Duke Commencement, 2009 May 10; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0070)
  - Duke Commencement, 2009 May 10; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0071)
  - Duke Commencement, 2010 May 16; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0074)
  - Duke Commencement, 2010 May 16; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0075)
  - Duke Commencement, 2011 May 15; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0084)
  - Duke Commencement, 2012 May 13; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0091)
  - Duke Commencement, 1992 May 17; 3/4-inch (Box 20, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0059)
  - Duke Commencement, 1992 May 17; 3/4-inch (Box 20, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0060)
  - Duke Commencement, 1991 May 10; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0042)
  - Duke Commencement, 1992 May 17; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0043)
  - Duke Commencement, 1993 May 16; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0044)
  - Duke Commencement, 1994 May 8; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0045)
  - Duke Commencement Address - Elizabeth Dole, 2000 May 14; betacam-sp (Box 20, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0119)
  - Duke Commencement Address - Jimmy Carter, 1997 May 18; betacam-sp (Box 20, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0115)
  - Duke Commencement Address - Oprah Winfrey, 2009 May 10; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0072)
  - Duke Commencement Address - Ted Koppel, 1987 May 10; 3/4-inch (Box 20, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0058)
  - Duke Commencement Address, Marian Wright Edelman, 1992 May 14; betacam-sp (Box 20, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0112)
  - Duke Founder's Day Convocation, 2001 May 13; DVCAM (Box 22, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0017)
  - Duke Founder's Day Convocation, 2010 September 30; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0077)
  - Duke Founder's Day Convocation, 2011 September 22; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0086)
  - Duke Founder's Day Convocation, 2011 September 22; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0087)
  - Duke Graduate School Convocation Service, 2004 August; DVCAM (Box 22, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0025)
  - Duke Graduate School Graduation Ceremony, 2008 May 10; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0066)
  - Duke Opening Day Convocation Service, 2003 August 21; betacam-sp (Box 22, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0009)
  - Duke Opening Day Convocation Service, 2004 August 19; DVCAM (Box 22, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0026)
  - Duke Opening Day Convocation Service, 2005 August 25; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0059)
  - Duke Opening Day Convocation Service, 2006 August 23; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0063)
  - Duke Opening Day Convocation Service, 1999 August 26; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0050)
  - Duke Opening Day Convocation Service, 2001 August 23; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0052)
  - Duke Opening Day Convocation Service, 2002 August 22; VHS (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0053)
  - Duke Opening Day Convocation Service, 1997 August 28; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0055)
  - Duke Opening Day Convocation Service, 2000 August 24; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0056)
  - Duke Opening Day Convocation Service, 2005 August 25; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0057)
  - Duke Spot #1, 1990s; betacam-sp (Box 20, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0109)
  - Duke Spot #2, 1990s; betacam-sp (Box 20, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0110)
  - Duke/JWT Spot, 1990s; betacam-sp (Box 20, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0111)
  - Freshman Convocation 2013, 2013 August 21; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0094)
  - Lecture - Fiona Terry, 2008 September 18; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0068)
  - Lecture - General Martin Dempsey in Page Auditorium, 2012 January 12; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0088)
  - Lecture - Jane Goodall in Page Auditorium, 2011 March 28; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0080)
  - Lecture - Jonathan Tisch in Griffith Film theater, 2010 October 19; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0078)
  - Lecture - Robert Gates in Page Auditorium, 2010 September 29; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0076)
  - Lecture - Temple Grandin in Baldwin Auditorium, 2011 February 21; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0079)
  - Lecture by John Ward Thomas, Chief of US Forestry Service, 1996 April 12; betacam-sp (Box 21, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0128)
  - Lecture by Kathleen A. McGinty, 1996 April 12; betacam-sp (Box 21, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0129)
  - Lefkowitz-Brodhead Event in Griffith Film Theater, 2012 November 1; XDCAM (Box 24, Video-disc UA10030003-XDCAM-0002)
  - MLK Address in Duke Chapel - Reverend William Turner, 2013 January 20; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0092)
  - Pratt School of Engineering, 2011 May 15; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0083)
  - Press Conference - Nobel Prize Winner Robert Lefkowitz, 2012 October 10; XDCAM (Box 24, Video-disc UA10030003-XDCAM-0001)
  - Seeds of Change Panel Discussion - Von Canon B, 2012 April 21; DVCAM (Box 23, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0089)
  - Service of Death and Rememberance for Dr. James H. Semans, 2005 April 26; betacam-sp (Box 22, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0011)
  - The Inauguration of Nannerl O. Keohane, 1993 October 23; betacam-sp (Box 20, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0121)